本作品由Norm HALFCD Team倾情奉献\N感谢原作提供资源.仅供学习交流.严禁用于商业行为\N请自觉于下载后24小时内删除!如果喜欢本片,请购买正版!
更多精彩 尽在www.NormTeam.com
压制:鬼谷子  字幕:鬼谷子\NCompression:GV-Sir  Subtitles:GV-Sir
飞天大盗 第1季第1集
S01E01 The Con is On
- 我来付小费 - 谢了
- I'll get the tip. - Thank you.
- 谢了 兄弟 - 保重
- Thanks,lad. - Keep well.
- 再见 - 再见
- Cheerio. - Bye.
把刀放下 伙计 安静一下 行吗?
Put the cleaver down,mate.Everybody calm down,all right?
你们真想翻身嘛 我这次可是通杀
If you all want to chance it,I'll tell you now,I've got a full house.
全押上 怎样?
All in,right?
- 你丢了这个 - 哦 非常感谢 伙计
- You dropped this. - Thank you very much.
请你一杯 怎么样?
Can I buy you a drink?
- 当然 没问题 - 想喝什么?
- All right,sure.Why not? - What'll you have?
- 威士忌 谢谢 - 一杯威士忌
- Scotch,thanks very much. - Scotch.
行了!
All right!
忙吗?
Busy?
Ash 找个轻松点的生财之道吧
Ash.There are easier ways to earn a living.
Mickey
Mickey.
太好了
How good!
不是在做梦吧
Have I missed you or what?
- 快车道上的生活不错嘛 - 还不错!
- How's life in the fast lane? - It's good.
这是城里唯一的生财之道了 不是边开车边吃汉堡包..
It's the only game in town.If they're not eating a hamburger...
就是在摆弄CD机..要么就是在接电话
or fiddling with the CD player,they're on the phone.
没人会注意路况的
No one watches the road anymore.
谢了 Eddie
Cheers,Eddie.
你呢 怎么样?
So what about you?How was it?
完全不同的经历 别提了
A new experience.One I don't care to repeat.
那现在在做什么呢?
So what now then?
算是收山之作了
I feel like one last score.
- 玩大的还小的? - 大的
- Long or short? - Long.
没人再敢玩大的了吧
No one is playing the long con anymore.
没人敢玩 是因为他们不会玩 一起来吧 最后一次了
They don't because they can't.Come on,one last time.
然后我就金盆洗手 功成身退 希望不会功败垂成
Then I'll stop.I'll retire on my terms.Not because I've been beat.
你知道 没有你 我做不到的
You know I can't do it without you.
- 什么时候开始? - 早开始了 Albert已经下套了
- When do we start? - Already have.Albert's got a mark.
不过 当务之急是 能搞定酒店吗?
But first things first.Can you swing a hotel?
小菜一碟!
Can Pavarotti sing?
我们已经在监视Stone了
We've already got Stone under surveillance.
- 是的 我知道 长官 - 那为什么还是窃贼猖獗?
- I understand that,sir. - Then why the heavy mob?
我们得到可靠情报 Stone正准备和新目标接头...
We've had intelligence Stone's next target is well connected...
高手间的较量
plays golf with the Chancellor.
看来他有个精英团队 为什么不先警示他?
So he's got friends in high places.Why don't you just warn him off?
一方面我们监督他....
Whilst we are keen to protect him...
一方面 我们希望Stone主动放弃
we're even more keen to see Stone put away again.
- 没别的选择了? - 没有
- Have I got a choice? - No.
好了 大家听着
All right,listen up.
这位是从总部来的监察探长 Martin DePalma
This is Detective Inspector Martin DePalma from Central.
他是来视察Mickey Stone的案子
He's here to oversee the Mickey Stone surveillance.
尽可能满足他的需要
Give him what he wants.
- 任何行动 先经过我的同意 - 是的
- Any overtime comes through me first. - Sir.
Terri Hodges警官 我负责这个案子
Sgt.Terri Hodges.I've been heading up the surveillance.
很好 先看看我们都知道些什么
Good.Then let's see what you've got.
好的 再见!
All right,cheers.
Ashley Morgan
Ashley Morgan.
道上人称Ash或"三只脚"
Colloquially known as Ash or "Three Socks."
- "三只脚"? - 在狱中得名
- Three Socks? - He got the name in prison.
就在他第一次从澡堂里出来之后
After his first visit to the shower block.
他是个百宝箱 不管你想要什么 Ash Morgan都弄得到
He's a fixer.Whatever you want,Ash Morgan will find it.
在10年前的一次酒吧打斗中 导致头骨骨折
He got a skull fracture in a barroom brawl 10 years ago.
然后他就以此为谋生之法
He uses it to work the flop.
假装被车撞 然后去医院.....
Bounces over a car,goes to hospital...
X光检查出骨折 保险公司理赔
x-ray shows the fracture,insurance company pays out.
Albert Stroller 赌场老手
Albert Stroller.Habitual gambler.
赌马 轮盘 纸牌 Albert都玩 他负责下套
Gee-gees,casinos,card games.Albert plays them all.He's the roper.
找到下手目标 骗取他的信任 再介绍给团伙的其他成员
He finds the marks,sucks them in,and introduces them to the mob.
通常以退役军人或退休银行家的身份
Usually plays the part of ex-serviceman or retired banker.
事实上 他是南美中西部的皮鞋销售商
In reality he was a shoe salesman in the American Midwest.
据说 他的商店倒闭后 员工过剩
Legend has it,when his store closed down and the staff made redundant...
他从银行骗了6万美金 并和他们的同伙平分
he conned the company out of $60,000 and shared it amongst his coworkers.
他在70年代逃往英国
He fled to England in the '70s...
初尝甜头之后 便一发不可收拾
but by then he'd got the taste and hasn't looked back since.
一旦Stroller找到了目标...
Once Stroller's got his mark...
骗局进入新流程
it's time to move up to the next level.
首脑人物
The insideman.
Michael Stone 也叫 "Mickey Bricks"
Michael Stone. Also known as "Mickey Bricks."
他总是单独行动 诈骗专家 从未失手过
He's in a class all on his own.A long con player.Never been convicted.
对所有的反诈骗探员来说...
It is a matter of personal pride...
找到证据并亲手逮捕他 将会是件非常值得骄傲的事
to every fraud investigator in the country,to be the one who nails him.
他因为一件无关的案件 在监狱里服役了2年 刚刚释放
Just finished his first spell in prison for an unrelated crime.He served two years.
传言 这次是他的收山之作 错过这次机会 游戏就结束了
Rumors are,this is his last score.We miss him this time,it's game over.
我们认为这是他们的新猎物
We think this is their next mark.
Peter Reginald Williams
Peter Reginald Williams...
80年代初期开始从事制药行业
started a pharmaceutical business in the early '80s.
他的第一任妻子Sara出生富豪世家
His first wife Sara was from old money.
他借用了她的家族关系 得到了许多政府的研究项目
He used her family's connections in the government to get research contracts.
- 从哪儿下手? - 他很贪婪
- Where's the in? - He is greedy.
- 我来付小费 - 谢谢
- I'll get the tip. - Thank you.
尽管他常常名列富豪榜的前500名
Regularly makes the Top 500 rich list.
但对于小钱却总是斤斤计较
But would cross the street to pick up ?coin.
最近他娶了个年轻漂亮的太太
He recently bagged himself a new young wife.
不过她大肆挥霍的程度 远远超出了他的预计
But she's high maintenance and spends his cash faster than he'd like.
他对漂亮脸蛋没有一点招架能力
He's generally a sucker for a pretty face.
花钱取悦她们 裙子越短 他给的越多
Spends money to impress.The shorter the skirt,the looser he gets.
听上去你对他很感兴趣 Albert
Sounds like you really warmed to this guy,Albert.
没错 此人贪婪成性 睚眦必报 （多谢老黑）
Yes.He's an objectionable little man,with the morals of an alley cat.
那正是你的目标
That's marks for you.
这个团伙不是骗养老金的小混混
This crew isn't about conning little old ladies out of their pension.
他们有严格的组织结构
They're strictly major league.
还有 要记得 Mickey Bricks 总以为他比我们聪明得多
And remember,Mickey Bricks thinks he's cleverer than us.
我们永远抓不到他的把柄
That there's no way we can catch him.
我们要证明 他错了
Let's prove him wrong.
是时候下手了
Time to get an edge.
Mickey
- 我忘了什么了吗? - 两年里就一通电话
- Did I miss something? - One phone call in two years.
是啊 你知道我讨厌占线
Yeah,you know how I hate queuing.
我已经集合到所有的人了
I've got the crew together.
所有的?
Everyone?
Albert?
我们出发了 是的 带他来吧
We're on.Yeah,bring him in.
别给他小费 Tony 他的服务太烂了
Don't tip him,Tony.That service was shite.
- 你的钱包掉了 - 不是我的
- You've dropped your wallet. - It's not mine.
不少钱啊
That's a lot of money.
看看 Mark Hamilton Clacy Hughes的股东
Let's see."Mark Hamilton.Clacy Hughes Associates."
你打算怎么办?找寻失主?
What do you say?Finders keepers?
说得没错 先看看他是不是住在这里
You are a card.Let's see if he's staying here.
我们在地上找到了这个
We found this on the floor.
先生 我会把这个还给Hamilton先生的
I'll see Mr.Hamilton gets it,sir.
不,我不这么认为 告诉我们他在哪个房间
No,I don't think so.Just tell us which room he's in.
- 她是谁? - Stacie Monroe
- Who's she? - Stacie Monroe.
她嫁给了Jake Henry 一个惯偷 诈骗犯
She was married to short con artist Jake Henry.
几乎都是诱惑手法 一直都很顺利
They worked the badger mostly.Did well,too.
然而 五年前 Jake卷了他俩所有的积蓄消失了
Then Jake took all their savings and ran for the hills five years ago.
真是个让人值得敬佩的贼
So much for honor amongst thieves.
别把结婚誓言当真了
Not to mention your wedding vows.
谣传 Stone在遇到他老婆前 跟她有过一腿
Word is,she and Stone had a thing once.Before he met his wife.
不单有张漂亮的脸 她也是个高手
Not just a pretty face.She's sharp.
在Stone的团队里也是出类拔萃的
Maybe even in Stone's league.
是谁?
Who is it?
- Mr.Hamilton? - 您是哪位?
- Mr.Hamilton? - Who wants to know?
我想我们发现了您的东西
We think we found something of yours.
您的钱包
Your wallet.
3块5
3.50.
给你两次机会找到――"她"
I'll give you two gos to find the lady.
- 可以 行 3块5 - 拿去吧
- Yeah,right.3.50. - Take that.
你不该在这里混 Danny
Shouldn't you be somewhere,Danny?
这样吧 简单点
Tell you what,I'll make it easy for you.
我把这个Q的一个角折起来 象这样
I'll take the Queen,turn the corner up.Like that.
开始了
Here we go.
选一张 不来钱 你错了 就请我喝一杯
Choose.No money.If you get it wrong,just buy me a drink.
- 再来一杯 - 真是个讨人厌的家伙
- Same again,please. - You're a very sick person.
只是天赋而已
Just naturally gifted.
听说了嘛 Mickey Bricks放出来了
You heard Mickey Bricks is out?
- 那个诈骗行家? - 最终的赢家
- Plays the long con,right? - Top of the food chain.
怎么样?你认为他能教我些什么?
So what?You reckon he could teach me something?
我怎么知道?你们这帮家伙都让我崇拜
What do I know?All you guys freak me out.
不过 他们都说他是最棒的
But they say he's the best.
他现在住在London Park酒店
He's booked in the London Park Hotel.
- 想要什么? - 一杯威士忌
- Yes,mate? - Whiskey,please.
谢谢
Thank you.
为你们干杯 先生们
Here's to you,gentlemen.
我一直认为世界上 不可能再有诚实的人了
I didn't think there were any honest men left in the world.
- 仅剩一两个了吧 - 那就为诚实的人们干杯!
- One or two. - Here's to honest men.
- 该让我好好的感谢你们一番 - 不 不 我们不是冲这个来的
- You must let me thank you properly. - No.We wouldn't hear of it.
就当是回家的车费
Even if it's only the cab fare home.
稍等一下
Excuse me.
说到哪儿了?
Where were we?
哦 是的 我在极力说服你们 收取你们应得的回报
I was trying to persuade you to take something in return for your kindness.
是不是大家都认为"有钱能使鬼推磨"
It's a strange state of affairs
一旦有人做了拾金不昧的善举
if one chap can't do a favor for another...
反而会显得格格不入?
without money rearing its ugly head.
有一天你也会有机会来帮助我们的
One day you may be in a position to do something similar for us.
你知道 我有可能...我有个建议
You know,I just might.I have a suggestion.
明天有个贸易公司 想让我给他们一小笔投资
A business associate has asked me to make an investment for him tomorrow.
如果你们同意的话 算你们投资500英磅 如何?
If you'll allow me,I'll put in,say,?00 for you?
我把给你们的钱作为投资基金 你们等着收利润就行
I'll take the ?00 back,you just get to keep the profit.
那对我来说没什么损失
It'll have cost me nothing...
不过 我能感觉好点 好歹我为你们做了点事
but at least I'll feel happier knowing I've done something.
真是慷慨!
That sounds very generous.
就这样!
Good.
谢谢!
Thank you.
这项投资 我能问下是关于什么的吗?
This investment,can I ask what it is?
就是些股票什么 没什么新鲜的
Just stocks and shares.Nothing too exciting.
但愿是真的
Fingers crossed.
我确信 那并不重要
I'm sure that won't be necessary.
- 你觉得怎么样? - 我觉得象是个稳赚不赔的买卖
- What do you think? - Looks like a no-Iose situation to me.
我就喜欢这种
My favorite kind.
他们大约1小时前离开
They left about an hour ago.
Stroller离开Williams之后 又重新回到酒店
Stroller dropped Williams off,then went back to the hotel.
嗨 Mickey 很高兴...我是想...好吧 这样 轻松点
Hi,Mickey.Nice to...I was just...Okay,all right,take care.
嗨 Mickey 你好啊 我是Danny 我只是想...
Hi,Mickey.How're you doing?Danny.I was just...
这家伙显然很有兴趣
This guy moves in high circles.
我要找些特别的东西刺激下他
It'll take something special to impress him.
一旦Ash施展出他的魔法
That's exactly what he'll get.
他一定会如愿以偿的
As soon as Ash starts working his magic.
有没有想要找个年轻女郎 Albie?
Have you ever thought of a younger woman,Albie?
亲爱的 象我这样的年纪 还能想其他的吗?
My dear,at my age,I think of little else.
Stone先生 嗨 我是Danny Blue
Mr.Stone?Hi.Danny Blue.
很高兴见到你 也许你听说过我
Pleased to meet you.You've probably heard of me.
没有?好吧 我不是来搞破坏的 那我直接说重点吧
No?All right.I'm not gonna mess you about.I'll come straight to the point.
我知道你在做笔大买卖 我想加入
I know you're playing a score.I want in.
- 加入什么? - 加入..你知道的..这场游戏
- In what? - In.You know,in the game.
我想学 我真的很想学点东西 我想能不能进来聊一会
I want to learn.I really want to learn.I'll just come inside for a little chat.
房间很漂亮 不是吗?
This is nice,isn't it?
我很棒 我可以帮你 考虑一下吧 我愿意为你效劳
I'm good.I can help you.Think of it like that.I'll do that for you.
我了解所有的老把戏 你到哪一步了?
I know all the old plays.What're you doing?
设套?不是?下饵?收网?
The Wire?No?The Rag?The Pay-Off?
告诉我到哪儿了 我会跟上的 我能帮上忙
You tell me once,that's it.Bosh,it's in.
我猜你也看过《骗中骗》 是不是?
I bet you watched The Sting, too,didn't you?
《骗中骗》1973年电影
从没听说过
Never heard of it.
- 不 别把我拒之门外 - 我想我该这么做
- You're not gonna shut the door,are you? - Yeah,I thought I might.
什么时候收网?
So when do we pick them up?
等待时机
We wait.
我要拿到所有的东西
I want everything.
所有参与者,钱,不留一丝机会
All the players,the money.Nothing left to chance.
据我们所知...
As far as we can make out...
Mickey Bricks还没有足够的钱 来实施这次的诈骗
Mickey Bricks doesn't have the money to bankroll a con like this.
他们会外出敛财 那些靠小偷小摸而来的钱
They'll go out and try and raise what they can with short cons.
他们需要车 最高档的那种
They'll need a car,top of the range.
不会很显眼 但一定很显尊贵
Not too flash, but something that oozes class.
停车吗 先生?
Parking,sir?
- 给你 - 谢谢!
- Here. - Thank you.
显然上帝这次也站在他们这边
God help anyone who runs into them today.
抱歉!
I'm sorry.
240.
125.
够了?
Enough?
- 算房租吗? - 不算
- What about this place? - Sorted.
那就够了
Then it's enough.
先生们 正如我们约定的 我替你们投资了500英镑....
As promised,gentlemen,I invested the ?00 on your behalf...
这些...是你们的所得
and this is the return.
我希望没有令你们失望
I hope you're not disappointed.
哈 有1000英镑了吧?
There must be ?,000 here.
准确的说 是1950英镑
?,950,to be precise.
- 这份回报还真不错 - 我那份比你的要糟
- That's quite a return. - I've had worse.
我敢打赌 你一定赚翻了
Made quite a killing yourself,I'll wager.
绝对不会!
So shoot me.
别怪我多管闲事 不过我觉得...
Forgive me for prying,but I get the feeling...
这类的投资 难道连一点风险都没有吗?
there was little or no risk in this particular investment.
绝对不会有
No risk whatsoever.
那么 先生们 我要失陪一会 去开个会
So,if you'll excuse me,gentlemen,I do have a meeting.
等等 我在想 我们为什么不再投资一回?
Wait.I mean,why don't we go again?
再投资?
Again?
Tony Hamilton先生已经够慷慨了
Tony,Mr.Hamilton has been more than generous.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 有事吗? - 亲爱的 他在吗?
- Can I help you? - Love,is he in?
- 对不起 - 再见到你真是太好了
- Excuse me. - Good to see you again.
打扰了 先生们 你好吗?
Excuse me,gentlemen.How are you?
Hamilton先生 我想亲自与你握个手
Mr.Hamilton.I want to shake you by the hand.
你真是非常 非常的了不起 很抱歉 我曾经怀疑过你的能力
You are a very great man,and I'm sorry I ever doubted you.
当初我给你那笔钱的时候 有那么一刹那 我觉得....
When I gave you that money,I did,for one second,consider the possibility...
你有可能会..你知道的 我真不想再说出来了
that you could have been,you know...I can't even say it.
说吧 没关系 想说就说吧
Go ahead.Please.Get it off your chest.
我以为你可能会是个骗子
I thought you could have been one of those conmen.
我可能再也见不到他和那笔钱了 你们知道我说的什么
I might never see my money or him ever again.
结果 砰-- 眨眼工夫 全回来了 连本带利....
Then,bang-- suddenly full be sent return just high interest of
难以置信 我得喝一杯 亲爱的 请给我杯威士忌
Unbelievable.I need a drink.Scotch,please,darling.
忘了介绍 先生们 这是Redford先生 我的一个客户
I'm sorry,gentlemen.This is Mr.Redford,a client of mine.
Redford先生 这是Tony Monroe 和Peter Williams
Mr.Redford,this is Tony Monroe and Peter Williams.
Peter 你好
Peter,how do you do?
我还想再投资 这次我要加本金
I'm ready to go again,but this time I wanna go bigger.
可以 不过现在不合时宜...
Fine.But this is neither the time nor the place to...
我都准备好了
I'm ready.
Helen 替我送送Tony和Peter好吗?
Perhaps you'd like to show Tony and Peter out?
不 等等 我想...
No,wait.
如果有其他的投资机会 我也很想了解一下
If there's another deal up for grabs,I'd like to hear about it.
- Tony? - 当然 我也想听听
- Tony? - Absolutely,yes.
谢谢 明早我的司机会去接你
Thank you.My car will pick you up tomorrow morning.
谢了
Thank you.
我不是行家 不过...一切进展的很顺利
I'm no expert,but I'd say that went like a dream.
- 可以加入了? - 算你一份
- So am I in? - You're in.
谢谢!
Thank you.
出发!
Go.
我正在等几个新客户
Just waiting for some new clients...
来拜访105房间的Hamilton先生
here to see Mr.Hamilton in 105.
- 我查一下登记表 - 他们可能不在上面
- I'll check the list. - They might not be on it.
就算他们不在表上 我也要先查一下
If they're not on the list,I'll need to check.
105房间不是Moss先生的办公室吗?
Isn't 105 Mr.Moss's office?
- 你相不相信一见钟情? - 什么?
- Do you believe in love at first sight? - What?
别怕!嘘......
Don't panic.
你知道嘛 每天傻傻的看着你坐在这里
Do you know what it's like,watching you sitting here every day?
我只想要个蜻蜓点水般的亲吻 可以吗?
I just want an insy-winsy little kiss.Can I,please?
Hamilton先生正在等你们
Mr.Hamilton's expecting you.
- 这边走 - 谢谢
- Right this way. - Thank you.
明白 查到他的真实身份了
Got it.They've got a positive ID.
他叫Danny Blue 高明的小偷
He's a short con artist called Danny Blue.
犯罪记录?
Any history?
3个月前他在南部实施过一次诈骗
He played a con three months ago,south of the river.
不过 受害者撤消了控诉
But the mark withdrew his complaint...
CPS也没有证据提起诉讼
and CPS wouldn't prosecute without evidence.
为什么撤消了?
Why did he pull out?
受害者把毕生积蓄都花在赌马上了
The mark bet his life savings in a horseracing scam...
他的妻子却毫不知情
but his wife didn't know anything about it.
我想 他并不想让她知道
I suppose he wanted to keep it that way.
估计解释起来很费时间
Hard to explain over breakfast,I guess.
正如他们所说的:总有人会上钩的
It must be true what they say:"There's one born every minute."
先生们 请进!坐吧
Gentlemen,come in.Take a seat.
谢谢
Thank you.
抱歉 伙计 我来迟了
Sorry I'm late,guys.
遇到了个老朋友
Ran into an old friend.
先生们 欢迎来到"富饶之地"
Gentlemen,welcome to the land of plenty.
谢谢
Thank you.
接下来我所讲的事 或许是十分安全的
What I'm about to show you may be foolproof...
但也是违反法律的
but it's also illegal.
不会有人吃亏 但却违背了法律
There's no victim,but it's against the law.
你们还想继续听吗?
Would you like me to continue?
听好 诈骗守则之一
You see,the first rule of the con...
- 你不能欺骗老实人 - 绝对不可以
- ...is you can't cheat an honest man. - It's never been done.
- 不能这样做 - 绝对不行
- Can't happen. - Impossible.
那只会让你空手而归
It only works if you want something for nothing.
- 我们呢? - 我们会一本万利
- What do we do? - We give you nothing for something.
目前你得到了1000英镑
You're ?,000 up so far.
现在最好是 见好就收
It's a very good time to walk away.
- 但是他不会 - 因为他太贪婪了
- But he can't. - Because he's so greedy.
- 那么我们做什么? - 满足他的贪欲
- So what do we do? - Feed the greed.
不过他还有最后一次机会
But he's got one last chance.
我们告诉他那是违法的
We've told him it's illegal.
你可能血本无归
You could lose everything.
- 事业 妻子 家庭 - 最后进监狱
- Career,wife,home. - Prison.
你可以马上退出
Get out while you can.
聪明点吧!
Do the smart thing.
正如我所说的 我要告诉你们的事
As I was saying,what I'm about to show you...
也许毫无风险 但却是违法的
may be foolproof,but it's against the law.
现在 你们还想继续嘛?
Now,would you like me to continue?
嘿 制订法律不就是要人去违反嘛
Laws were made to be broken.
告诉Peterson午饭之前 给我所有的分析报告
Can you tell Peterson I want those breakdowns by lunchtime?
谢谢
Thank you.
所有的股票交易所 东京 纽约
Share transactions from Tokyo and New York...
通过电脑与伦敦相连
are relayed to the city of London by computer.
准确来说 通过我们的电脑
Or more precisely,our computer.
每当一跨国集团公布年报时 交易市场总会引起一阵骚动
When the multi-nationals publish their annual reports,there's a flurry of activity.
如果企业运作不错 吸引股民认购 股票价格上升
If a company does well,their shares attract buyers and the price jumps.
我们所做的就是 使交易延迟足够长的时间
We've managed to delay those transactions in the system long enough...
以便于我们在他们认购之前 买进我们所需要的份额
to assess them and put our own order in to buy before them.
所以 你购买那些一定会升值的股票?
So you buy,knowing the share prices are gonna go up?
- 没错! - 他们会发现交易延迟的吧
- Exactly. - They must notice the delay.
如果只是延迟1/10秒的话 就不会被发现
Not when it's less than nine-tenths of a second.
用不到一秒的时间做这些 行吗?
You can do this in less than a second?
那点时间够我们的主机运行3百万次
Our mainframe can make three million calculations in that time.
你能得到什么好处?
What's in it for you?
25%的利润
I take 25% Of your profit.
- 25%? - 不二价
- 25%? - Non-negotiable.
等等 利润是保证的 不是吗?
Hang on.The profit is guaranteed,right?
完全肯定 你们没有利润 我就没钱可赚了
Set in stone.If there's no profit,I don't get paid.
3天后 Vestron石油集团 会发布他们的年报
In three days,the oil company Vestron are releasing their annual report.
一旦公布 股票经纪人会席卷所有的新股
Once it's out,every major broker will be crawling all over those shares.
我们计划购买50万英镑的股票
The plan is to buy ?00,000 worth of shares.
两个客户已经各投资了10万
I have two investors already in place at ?00,000 each.
还剩下三个空缺
There are three places left.
10万?
?00,000?
很好 可以 算我一份
Great,yeah,I'm in.
我不知道能不能筹集到这么多钱...
I don't know if I can raise that kind of money...
不管你上不上船 三天后起航 Tony?
The boat leaves in three days.Either you're on it,or you're not.Tony?
的确数目不小 不过我会弄到的
It's a lot of money,but I'll find it.
不介意我打个电话给我的经纪人吧?
You don't mind if I call my broker?
我只说不能离开这个房间
What I've just said can't leave this room.
我不习惯投资我从没听说过的公司
I'm not in the habit of investing in companies I've never heard of.
George?Peter Williams 关于Vestron你知道多少?
George?Peter Williams.What do you know about Vestron?
不 没什么 只是听到些传言 就这样
No problem.Just heard a whisper,that's all.
不 有问题再找你
No.I'll call you if anything comes of it.
好的 算我一份
Count me in.
很好 还有件事...
Good.One more thing...
我不想留下任何书面凭据 必须准备现金
I don't want to leave any paper trails.The money has to be in cash.
- 现金? - 有问题吗?
- Cash? - Problem?
- 我想没有 - 很好
- I suppose not. - Good.
感谢你给我这次机会
I just want to thank you for this opportunity.
- 我也是 - 谢谢
- Likewise. - Thank you.
施点魔法
Work the spell.
好啊
How're you doing?
省省力气吧 我不会和工作伙伴发生关系的
Save us both a little time.I don't screw people I work with.
- 不吗? - 不
- No? - No.
针对每个人...
Does that go for everyone?
还是某一群人而已?
Or just the troops?
给你个忠告 Danny 朋友的建议
Do you want a little tip,Danny?Some friendly advice?
行 那太好了
Yeah,that would be great.
边看边学 少管那些不归你管的事
Watch and learn.Stay out of things that don't concern you.
- 大家都在各忙各的 - 你很快就能融入这个大家族了
- Your guys seem pretty tight. - After a while,you get to be family.
很好笑吗?
I say something funny?
不是 这个家族并不是为我而生
No.The whole family thing works for me.
你只是干小偷小摸的勾当 Danny
You play short cons,Danny.
只会趁周末掏空别人的工资袋 你不会理解我们在干的事
Emptying people's wage packets on a Friday night.You wouldn't understand.
- 可以提个意见吗? - 当然
- Can I make a criticism? - Okay.
100,000
100,000?
我们能从那家伙身上搞到更多的钱
We can take this guy for a lot more than that.
那正是你需要学的
That's the bit you don't get.
并不是钱多钱少的问题
It's not just about the money.
- 什么时候学? - 一直...
- Since when? - Since always.
你不明白其中的道理 你什么也得不到
You don't get that,you don't get anything.
我的长辈一直就是这么做的
My old man was as straight as they come.
安于现状 悠于生活
Never wanted much and life didn't disappoint him.
他每天工作,吃饭,睡觉
He worked,ate,slept.
按时纳税 中规中矩
Paid his taxes on time,toed the line.
唯一的希望是能在60岁退休
The only dream he had was retiring at 60.
结果就在60岁生日的前三天
Dropped dead in the Post Office three days before his 60th birthday.
在邮局付电话帐单时 撒手人寰
He was paying his phone bill.
- 真遗憾 - 是的 我也觉得
- I'm sorry. - Yeah.Me,too.
你想做个普通人 是吗?
You want to be regular people?Do you?
那就只能边抱怨工作的平凡无奇
Go do that.They're crying out for foot soldiers down there.
边为那些老板,银行家,政客们卖命 仅此而已
Go and have your life run by bosses,bank managers,and politicians.
但如果你真打算当个诈骗高手...
But if you want to be a grifter...
不要带上任何 你无法及时摆脱的累赘
don't have anything in your life you can't walk away from in a second.
爱人 朋友 甚至你的至亲
Lovers,friends,even your own mother.
那你妻子呢?
What about your wife?
我听说了
I heard what happened.
她想我做的 我做不到
She wanted me to be something I wasn't.
我努力的不让她失望
And I was desperate not to disappoint her.
谁想到 后患无穷
Recipe for disaster.
如果你俩还在一起的话...
If you were still together...
你能够做到对她视若无睹吗?
you're telling me you could just walk away from her?
首要原则 Danny
First rule,Danny:
人不为己 天诛地灭
Always look after number one.
人人都会这么做的
If you don't,no one else will.
好的 我会铭记在心的
I'll try and remember that.
回去吧 Danny 去休息会
Go home,Danny.Get some sleep.
Danny Blue?
Danny Blue.
那孩子今天干得不错
The kid did well today.
让我想起了当初的你
Reminds me of you.
焦躁不安...
Worryingly.
行了 别说了
Okay,come on.
你怎么找到他的?
How did you find him?
- 我有表现得这么明显吗? - 是你把我调教得太好了
- Am I that transparent? - You taught me well.
我听说过他 他很棒
I heard about him.He's good.
渴望成为行内最出色的
Wants to be the best.
是不是听起来很熟悉?
That sound familiar?
我让Eddie暗示他来找你
I told Eddie to point him in your direction.
不管怎么说 我做到了
I'm all but done anyway.
- 你打算不管他? - 我们都在努力摆脱
- You going to miss it? - We're all trying to get out.
如果你能做别的 你也想摆脱这种生活 不是嘛
You would,too,if you could think of something else to do.
好啊 伙计们
All right,boys.
知道我为什么喜欢轮盘赌?
You know what I love about roulette?
不到最后一秒 不知胜负结果
That glorious 30 seconds while the wheel is still spinning.
Christopher Rawlings
Christopher Rawlings.
因为那次赌马
The horseracing scam.
他妻子发现他输了所有的积蓄
His wife found out he'd lost their life savings.
他正在准备起诉
He's ready to press charges.
你坐过牢 是吧 Danny?
You ever been to prison,Danny?
- 你们不是该录音吗? - 那是B计划
- Shouldn't you be taping this? - That's Plan B.
- 想知道A计划吗? - 真让人吃惊
- Want to hear Plan A? - Surprise me.
我们有足够的证据送你们进监狱 没人能躲开法律的制裁
We've already got enough to send everyone down.No way around that.
不过 想想受害者是谁?他的权力.....
But bearing in mind who the mark is,the powers that be...
不会让审判拖太久
would rather not have a lengthy trial.
他会觉得这些内幕太不堪
They think the details might be embarrassing.
他不想被别人知道太多实情 当然 会主动承认犯罪事实
What they need is a watertight case so overwhelming,everyone pleads guilty.
匆匆宣判之后 这件事不久就被人遗忘了
We'll rush the sentencing through and the whole thing blows over.
听上去你们都盘算好了
Sounds like you've got it all worked out.
是的
We have.
我们知道你很晚才加入 所以你还有一线生机
We know you came into the game late.So you get a lifeline.
- 什么机会? - 不动声色 依旧干你的活
- Which is? - Just do what you've been doing.
被捕后 我们会给你个藏身处 然后给我们一份证词
After the arrests,we take you to a safe house,you make a statement.
一旦其他人知道 我们取得了确凿的证据
Once the team knows we've got your evidence...
他们知道除了承认有罪 别无他法
they'll know they can't do anything but plead guilty.
作为回报 你将会被无罪释放
In return,you walk away into the sunset.
如果我不合作呢?
What if I don't?
如之前所说 和其他人一起进监狱
Like I said,you go down with the rest of them...
而且会考虑追加Rawlings一案
and we'll add the Rawlings job for good measure.
你所做的就是回去 假装我们从来没遇到过
All you have to do is go back,pretend we never had this conversation.
不管你做什么 Mickey和其他人 都会进监狱的
Mickey and the others are going to prison whatever you do.
对于你来说 你有选择的机会 是否要跟他们一起进监狱?
The only choice you have to make is whether you go with them or not.
放聪明点 Danny
Be smart,Danny.
人不为己 天诛地灭
Look after number one.
- 那孩子呢? - 他会来的
- Where's the kid? - He'll be here.
打起精神了
Opening night nerves.
Williams已经上路了
Williams is on his way up.
你好
Gentlemen.
你迟到了
You're late.
- 对不起 - 没关系 就一会工夫
- I'm sorry... - Doesn't matter.There's no time.
我们开始吧
Let's get this done.
- Redford呢? - 他会来的
- Where's Redford? - He'll be here.
我以为我们是一起开始的
I thought we were all going to do this together.
如果你觉得有问题的话 我们可以取消所有计划
If there's a problem,we can call the whole thing off.
他来了
Here he is.
听着 Mickey...
Look,Mickey...
警察!所有的人不要动!
Armed police!Everybody stay exactly where you are!
把箱子放下!
Put the case down!
把手举过头顶!
Everyone,hands on heads.
到底出了什么事?
What the hell is going on?
先生 这个是个骗局 你上当了 什么?
You've been caught up in a confidence trick,sir.
这些人打算榨干你所有的钱
These men are planning to swindle you out of your money.
一定是搞错了
There must be some mistake.
行了 Danny 没你的事了
All right,Danny.You can go.
叛徒!
Judas.
听着 事实不是这样的
Listen,this is not how it looks.
把箱子拿过来
Get the cases.
别这样 Michael
Don't do it,Michael.
最后一课 Danny
Final lesson,Danny.
我说真的
I mean it.
- 哦 天哪! - 把他弄出去!
- Oh,God! - Get him out of here.
该死!
Bastard!
- 我们需要你的证词 - 我也有我考虑立场
- We need a statement. - I have my position to think of.
- 先生 我们理解 - 把钱还给我 我立马走
- We understand that,sir. - Just give me my money and I'll go.
- 我们不能这么做 那是证据 - 该死的钱 我要离开这里
- We can't do that,it's evidence. - Sod the money.Let me out of here.
我不能被牵连到这种事里去 那会毁了我的
I can't be implicated in something like this.It'll ruin me.
如果我们有足够的证据 就可以提起诉讼
If we have enough evidence,we can get guilty pleas.
- 你不需要出庭 - 我被逮捕了吗?
- It won't go to court. - Am I under arrest?
- 我们需要你的证词 - 我是不是被捕了?
- We need your statement. - Am I under arrest?
没有 先生
No,sir.
给我让开!
Get out of my way.
让他走
Let him go.
希望他清楚 他该做些什么
Let's hope the boss can do his stuff.
很抱歉 弄伤了你
Sorry about the head.
- 你杀了他 - 我救了你一命 Danny
- You killed him. - I saved your life,Danny.
他们被拘留了
Everyone's in custody.
回警察局时 我带你去检查下
We'll get you checked out on the way to the station.
现在 有足够的时间结束我们的交易
First,time to keep your end of the bargain.
确保没有任何遗漏
Be sure not to miss anything out.
我没有背叛他们
I'm not a grass.
放聪明点 Danny
Be smart,Danny.
现在你只能认输了
All you can do now is lose.
所以 我输了
Then I lose.
迟早 我会好好整整象你这样 卑鄙无耻的家伙
I'd sooner that than hook up with a murdering scumbag like you.
- Stone企图杀了你 - 他以为我背叛了他
- Stone fired a gun at you. - He thought I'd betrayed him.
的确是 不然你就要进去蹲上五年
You do this,or I'll see you get five years.
最后一次机会
Last chance.
你去死吧!
Go screw yourself.
好的 他合格了
Okay,he's all yours.
我就知道你很棒 孩子
I knew you'd be okay,kid.
- 我还没加入? - 现在 算上你了
- I don't get it. - You're all right.
祝贺你!
Congratulations.
Sarge 那些犯人已经被释放了
Sarge,the prisoners you asked for are gone.
什么意思?被释放了?
What do you mean,they've gone?
谁保释的?
Who signed them out?
这里显示是D.I.DePalma
It says here D.I.DePalma.
别这样 Michael
Don't do it,Michael.
最后一课 Danny
Final lesson,Danny.
我说真的
I mean it.
给你看些东西
I got something for you.
不知道怎么回事 就去搞清楚
If you don't know,find me someone who does.
我想知道是谁派DePalma来的
I wanna know who sent DePalma over here.
谁下的命令 谁是他的长官
Who gave him his orders,who his superior officer is.
不 不用给我回电 我现在就要和他说话
No,you will not phone me back.I wanna speak to someone there now.
Danny Blue Neil Cooper
Danny Blue.Neil Cooper.
这个家伙 人称"诈骗艺术家"
This man defines the term "con artist."
我刚加入 很高兴能帮上忙
I'm just passing through.Glad I could help.
等一下!你对我开枪了?
Hang on a minute.You shot at me.
是的 不过我射偏了 记得吗?
Yeah,but I missed,remember?
所以我们现在是自由的
You're telling me we're home free?
绝对没错 除非警方想上庭解释
Absolutely.Unless the police would like to go to court...
为什么会又罪犯 领导了这次调查工作
and explain how the investigation was led by one of the accused.
这就是原因 孩子
It's all in the detail,kid.
干杯!
A toast.
为Mickey Bricks的最后一案!
To Mickey Bricks' last score.
一个时代的落幕
The end of an era.
最甜蜜的谎言就是 一个骗子欺骗了另一个
The sweetest con of all is to con another grifter.
而事实上 他不应该会上当
One who should know better.
你是说 你并不打算收手?
You mean you're not retiring?
我必须得找个理由 集合你们所有人
I had to say something to get you all together.
你个小恶魔
You little devil.
真是太聪明!
That's brilliant.
那不仅仅是钱的问题 Mickey?
It's not all about the money,is it,Mickey?
第一堂课结束了!
Here endeth the first lesson.